我在录像
谢谢，Connie！
OK，是56383
5-6-3
快点放歌啊，P！
[未完成]我等不及了
Amethyst，我很努力了
Steven,你确定是“车牌”是对的吗？
我一直在尝试输入但并没有播放
哦，你得点“开车”
原来如此
爽！Connie，歌开始了
要不...你们先唱
你确定吗？
没什么，总得有人录像吧？
Oh...好吧（我是程序狗，翻译烂别骂我）
我难免引人注目
I can't help it if I make a scene,
即使走下我的艳粉礼车
Stepping out of my hot pink limousine.
我甩甩头就能阻塞车流
I'm turning heads, and I'm stopping traffic,
万众为造型尖叫，为玩笑捧腹
When I pose, they scream, and when I joke, they laugh.
我有一双令人失神的眼
I've got a pair of eyes that they're getting lost in,
魔鬼的步伐迷惑人心
They're hypnotized by the way I'm walking,
犹如魔术师般炫目
I've got them dazzled like a stage magician,
万众望我所指，听我谈笑风生When I point, they look, and when I talk, they listen, well,
大家都需要朋友
Everybody needs a friend,
而我有你和你和你
And I've got you and you and you
如此之多都忘记名字
So many, I can't even name them,
谁叫我如此有名
Can you blame me? I'm too famous.
Connie？Connie，来吧，高潮要出来了
Oh,没什么，你们玩的High就好
来吧，该你了
你确定？
Yeah！玩玩吧
好吧，谢谢，Garnet
你是否注意我是那天上明星？
Haven't you noticed that I'm a star?
当地球旋转我进入你的视野
I'm coming into view as the world is turning.
你是否注意到我已如此成功？
Haven't you noticed I've made it this far?
现在所有人能看我闪耀
Now, everyone can see me burning.
Connie，唱的不赖嘛
谢谢，Pearl
你真是个K歌禽兽啊
Oh，谢谢夸奖，我只是...
呃...Pearl?
你点播放前添加了多少次？
大概有十五次吧？
I'm core！
Yeah