我们，是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文！
and Steven!
与洋葱头为友
翻译
零九/presisco
校对
BBBB
特效
CCCC
压制
DDDD
Yes! Perfectly timed afternoon sandwich complete.
Wait, I can't eat such a perfect sandwich
all on its own.
It needs a side.
But what?
Oh, hey, Amethyst. I made lunch.
You want to eat this empty container?
No, thanks.
O-okay.
You seen Garnet or Pearl?
Nope.
Any idea where they might be?
I don't know.
Somewhere not talking to each other.
Hmm.
Wait, I know what this meal needs.
A bag of...
Onion?!
What the...
Oh, no, you don't.
Onion!
We just put that screen in!
Come back here!
Those were going to complete my perfect lunch!
It's a special flavor
that's only in stores for a limited time!
I know how you are with food!
You're not even gonna eat them!
At least let me have just one!
This is it, Onion. Nowhere to hide.
Now just -- just drop the bag and --
uh...Onion?
Uh...
Amethyst?
Uh...That's really weird!
Um, so...I always knew Onion was weird, but...
I think he's obsessed with you?
What do you think, Amethyst?
Woman: Who's in there?
Now, I don't know how you got past that tarp,
but this is private property.
Vidalia?!
Amethyst?!
It's been years!
Man, you've changed.
You look terrible!
You look the same...
Terrible!
Wait, what?
Who's she? How do you know each other?
Oh, we both kind of hung around your dad,
but Vidalia's cooler than your dad,
so we started hanging out without him.
Is that Steven? Look at him.
He looks just like Greg.
That's good. That's good. He used to be super hot.
Uh, so did you paint these when you used to hang out?
Yeah, some of them. Some are new, though.
Amethyst was my favorite model.
Can you still turn into anything?
Anything but respectable.
Oh, man, we used to get into all sorts of trouble.
Now tell me, Steven,
aren't we just the spitting image of mischief?
Hardly.
You're wearing slippers.
You don't know what I've done in these shoes.
It's great to see you again.
Sorry it's been so long.
I guess we've both been busy.
Oh, yeah. I get it -- kids.
What about kids?
Oh, here's one now.
You're Onion's mom?!
Yep.
He's my little troublemaker.
And, Steven, he loves talking about you.
Oh, that's a great idea!
Steven, Amethyst, Onion wants to know
if you'd like to stay for dinner.
Um
We'd love to,
Right, Steven? Onion's, like, your best friend.
Now, tell me what you did in those shoes, girl.
Mm, I can't eat another bite of
Whatever that was.
Oh, it's just a little dish
I like to call noodles and butter.
I can't believe how long it's been.
I mean, check this guy out.
I used to be bigger than him.
Do you ever hear from old farty Marty?
Hm?
I don't know where that fool is.
Don't care, either.
It's just been me and Yellowtail for a while now.
What?!
Yellowtail?
Yeah, things just kind of happened.
Next thing you know, I'm living with a fisherman.
You should see your face right now.
Hey, Sour Cream.
I just didn't expect any of this.
Well, that's just how it is now.
So where's old fish tail at?
Uh, it's Yellowtail.
He spends a lot of time out at sea.
Hey, it's me.
Dude, you used to complain so much
about the smell at the docks.
It used to be so gross over there.
Now there are all these fancy boats hanging around.
Remember when we snuck on to the mayor's boat and trashed it?
Why do you hate food?
Yeah, I remember.
What about you, Amethyst?
Huh?
You haven't said a word about yourself all night.
Well, that's because my life is boring.
All right, how are the gems?
I don't know. They're boring, too.
Okay, thanks for dinner. Time to go, right, Amethyst?
What's the hurry? We got nothing to do.
'Sides, an amethyst/vidalia party don't end
till the sun come up.
Onion: Ma-ma.
What's that?
Oh, that's a great idea!
Steven, Onion wants to show you around the house.
What do you say? Can Onion tote you around?
Uh... W-what's going on?
Oh, whenever Sour Cream starts deejaying,
it uses all the electricity in the house.
Good thing Yellowtail's not here --
it drives him nuts.
Dude, your house is jacked.
What can you do? Kids got to express themselves.
You too, Onion.
Very expressive.
Looks like he's ready for you, Steven.
Uh... Cool shopping cart.
Why don't you just jump up and down on that trampoline?
I mean, it's, like, right there.
But it's your room...
...So do whatever you want.
You have a little mousy roommate friend!
Aww!
Oh.
Is that your pet?
Oh, that must be where he lives, right?
Let me help you put him in his home.
This is a pretty large container for a little baby --
snake!
Onion, you want me
to feed our little friend to this snake, huh?
Oh.
Sorry, but we all got to eat.
I...
Can't!
Ugh! Just take him from me!
I-I'll be over here.
Uh...
You don't have any more weird pets to show me, do you?
You gonna put on a movie?
That'd be nice -- and not creepy at all.
Cool hospital setting.
Vidalia: Okay, I'm ready.
Hey, that's your mom.
I'm ready!
What's she getting ready for?
Oh.
Oh, Yellowtail, I think...
Oh, it's happening!
Ugh, wait! What's going on?!
Here he comes!
"Happy Birthday Onion."
Is this you being born?!
Oh, I am never doing this --
I can't take much more of this.
Where?
Okay, I'm out.
Can't do this anymore. Need to go home.
Amethyst, I'm sorry, but it's time to --
Everything is a mess,
even Garnet, like, I've never seen Garnet this upset.
It's awful at home. I feel trapped.
That's crazy. I know what you mean, though.
You do?
Hey, we don't always get along in this family.
Yellowtail and Sour Cream are always at each other's throats.
It makes me nuts.
Actually, when I get like that,
I think about you
and how you could always just roll with it.
What?!
No! That was you!
You were so...Cool.
I was just like...A dumb sponge following you around.
But you were down for anything, not afraid of anything.
You know how much I wanted to be like you?
Ugh. I still think about it.
To be honest, that's why I started painting you again.
I'm -- I'm inspired by you, Amethyst.
Oh, looks like I'm gonna need more tea.
You want to eat this bag?
Yeah, my favorite.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Good thing the kids are keeping themselves busy.
Okay, Onion, let's do this.
Whatever weird or horrible thing you have planned for me,
I can take it.
Hey, slow down.
Oh, boy. This is gonna be bad.
Uh, uh, Onion, where are you?
What's this room?
Oh!
What's in there? Something horrible?
Onion! It's full of guys!
Wow!
I've never seen this red variant of ninja guy before.
You have gals, too?!
Hard hat gal!
Triangle gal!
Orange gal!
Karen!
Karen...
How'd you get a hold of -- no, don't tell me.
Hmm?
No way!
It's explorer gal!
She's so cool-looking!
Thanks for showing her to me --
you -- you should take your explorer gal back.
Are you giving this to me?
I can't believe it!
Thank you so much, Onion!
Aw, man! What other gals and guys you got?!
Ha, cool -- invisible guy.
And stay out.
Um, thanks for dinner -- and for listening.
Well, thanks for breaking into my house.
And don't worry about that other stuff.
It's gonna blow over.
You're a rock.
That's what you are, right?
Uh, something like that.
Well, whatever you are, don't be a stranger.
Yeah, I can stop by anytime if you need inspiration.
Or if you want,
you could come over to the temple sometime, too.
You could even bring Onion for Steven to hang with.
Oh, well, that sounds great to us.
What about you, Steven?
You ready for another round with this guy?
Yeah, we'll see.
你
♪ You
爱，如你
♪ love like you