Pearl?!Amethyst?! Garnet?!
You don't have toyell, Steven. We're right here.
I know, but Ifinished this drawing, and I
wanted to show it to you.
- Oh! Uh, of course.- All right!
Ha ha!Guitar Dad teaches you guitar!
- What is that?- It's my dad!
He's going to start teaching
guitar lessons, and hemade me his P.R. department.
- What's that stuff in his mouth?- Those are his teeth.
What are the lightning bolts for?
Uh...well, I-I was trying to show
that dad really rocks on theguitar, and ...
Then there should berocks falling out of the guitar.
I hear what you're saying,but it's too late for notes.
This is permanent marker.
- Mm-hmm!- What's that cute flyer for, Steven?
It's for my dad!He'll teach you guitar.
You guys want to sign up?My dad's really good!
Maybe I'll stop by and check it out.
Here, let me give you a flyer and ...
- Welcome to the big donut!- Hey, Buck!
Oh! What?Buck, Buck, Bu-u-u-u-ck!
Ha ha!What's going on, man?
What can we get for you today?
- Can I get a caprese salad?- Oh, sorry, Buck,
- we only serve don...- Do-nut worry, Buck!
I'll whip you up a salad ...no sweat! I'll be right back!
Lars, we don't even havevegetables here!
- Heh, what's a Guitar Dad?- Like my flyer? It's for my dad!
He'll teach you guitar!
Here, take one of these with you!Actually, just wear it!
- Are you ticklish?- This would make a rad shirt, man.
- Really?- Yeah! Let's make your flyer into T-shirts!
Oh, man!My dad would love that!
Gimme five on it.Oh, you missed.
Ho! I think it's swell you're
returning to the familybusiness, son!
Gonna help the old man getre-elected again, eh?
- Aw, son!- Ugh!
It's not for campaign stuff, dad.
Steven and I are making art.
Art!
Art, huh?I don't understand it myself,
but a boy's got to haveinterests and ambitions!
This stuff can beused to make T-shirts?
Oh, yeah, I've got all thelatest, state-of-the-art
screen-printing equipmentfrom years of
campaigning and othersome-such mayorly things.
Like this week, I'mcommemorating a bench!
"Welcome to...'Bench' City"? Thrifty!
- Dad, you can't use this!- Why not?
You know, I got to "gank dat"youth vote, boyeeee!
- Dad, stop.- What's this?
What have you got there?
I haven't seen this in years!
Remember when you drew this, Buck?
You couldn't wait to show itoff to all your little
- montessori friends.- Okay, dad! Thanks for all your help.
- See you later! Bye.- All right, kids!
I mean, peace in theMiddle East, Holmes!
- So cool.- Let's just get started already.
- Swag.  - Now everyone'sgonna want lessons from dad!
This is bigger thanyour dad, Steven. It's art.
And it's gonna flood the publicconsciousness.
Well, let's starthanding them out!
Too simple.We need to get controversial.
We need to create ...Boom! ... a scene.
Scanning for targets.
T-shirt cannon loaded and ready!
Beep, beep, beep... bibibibi!
- Sour Cream sighted!- Wom wom... wom wom wom.
Get ready! Take aim!
- And..- Womp womp womp... womp!
What in the world?Oh, this is the coolest thing
I've ever been hit in the head with!
Ronaldo spotted.Take aim!
Whoa! What the heck?!Huh?
Whoa! Weird!
Some kind of extraterrestrialspace dad guitar shirt?
So, you've finally decided tomake first contact, huh?
Where are you?!
Lars sighted.Take aim!
Youch! What the...What is this garbage?
Buck made this?
This is hilarious!Thanks, Buck!
Cheers!
Buck, this was such a good idea!
I don't know why we didn'tcollaborate on a project sooner!
This will make my dad so happy!
I can't wait to see the look onhis face when I stop by later.
Yeah.Should be good for a laugh.
Huh?Why would it be good for a ...
- Girl! Check out my new shirt!- It's really cute!
- Where'd you get it?- I don't know.
It just landed in front of mewhen I was out walking.
Well, if I were you, Iwouldn't wear some random shirt
that just fell out of the sky.What if there were bugs in it?
Relax!Who cares where it came from?
This shirt is the funniest thingI've seen in my life!
Looks like our shirt hasa really good buzz going.
Yeah, but I thinkthey think it's a joke.
Heh. The onlything that's important
is that they're talking about it.
- That's how real art works.- Oh, well, I-I guess you're right.
- Uh, how's this?- Ha ha ha. So bad.
Okay! Let's get startedwith the first lesson!
Have a seat and grab a ...Where you going?
Oh, uh, I guess he got animportant text or something.
- How's it been going today?- Really great!
Lots of people have beencoming by, thanks to your
- T-shirts, little guy.- That's great, dad!
- I'm really glad I could help ...- Yoo-hoo! Guitar Dad!
I just wanted to say I thinkyou're wonderful and hilarious!
Uh... thank you?
Huh. That's kind of strange.
- What is?- Well, lots of people have
stopped by, but no one'staken a lesson yet.
- What? Really?!- Ah, maybe they're just
checking out the scene before
they come back to get a real lesson!
- Buck!- Hey, there's my main man.
The shirts aren't working, Buck!
Yeah, they are.People love 'em.
But nobody wantsguitar lessons from my dad!
- That's not the point.- What?! Then what is the point?
The point is, it's an amazing shirt.
Aw, my drawing's not that good.
- Yeah, no. It's terrible.- What?!
That's what's so great about it.Your work is so naive.
You really love your dad.It's funny.
I... I don't want tomake these shirts anymore.
Too bad, Steven.It's so current, you can't stop it.
I'm a taste maker, and I'mgonna keep making tastes...
- forever.- Forever?
Well, forever, after I goto my dad's lame bench
commemoration. Peace.
- Garnet! Pearl! Amethyst!- Steven!
- What is it?!- Whoa, where's the fire?!
It's an emergency!You have to help me get rid
of all the shirts and stop Buckfrom making more!
Have the shirts cometo life and possessed the bodies
- of their wearers?- No, they just ...
Are people catchingon fire when they put on
- the magic shirts?- No, no, th-they're just ...
Are the shirtsdestroying the wearers' wills to
continue on in this mortal coil,
- thereby shutting down Beach City?!- No!!
They're... They're just
using my art in a wayI don't agree with.
- Oh.- Eh, we'll pass.
What?! But...But, I really need your help!
Steven, this soundslike a very abstract problem.
It's notsomething we can punch.
You must learn to help yourself.That's how you become stronger.
- Good point, good point.- Oh, absolutely.
- But!- You'll figure something out, Steven!
Yes, why not dust off thoseconflict-resolution skills!
Let your problem be known.
Then you can worktowards an understanding.
Oh, I'll make him understand.
- I'll make them all understand!- Eh, he'll be fine.
Okay. Is everyone here?
Hello! I was supposedto write a speech to,
um, commemorate this,uh, new bench, but
what had happened was Iran out of printer ink in
my printer that I keep at home.
So, I went to the store andwouldn't you know it?
They didn't carry the brand Iwas looking for, so...
- Bye!- ...I called up a buddy of
mine who owed me a...
few political favors,and he wasn't home!
Look out!
No!
I've been... shirt!
Buck... did you make this?
This shirt is genius!
This is way funnier than Guitar Dad!
This bench is actuallypretty comfortable.
Anyone elsestop by for lessons today?
So far, no, but, I'msure it'll pick up tomorrow!
Yeah, I'm sure it will.This is for you, by the way.
This is the last one, so it'ssuper-limited edition!
Aw, sweet!Thanks, Steven!
Yo, Steven, just wanted tosay, uh, I'm sorry for what
- I did and uh...- It's okay, Buck.
You don't have to sayany more than that.
You're a cool cat, Steven Universe.
Hey, Mister "U."?
You want to take a picturewith me or some junk?
No way, man.
I want a lesson...from Guitar Dad!