我们,是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
请替换
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
AAAA
校对
BBBB
特效
CCCC
压制
DDDD
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
They're the team you love to hate, but also hate to love.
I love wrestling!
Ooh! Another devastating move by Purple Puma
and Tiger Millionaire tonight, folks.
Mr. Smiley: Looks like Shark-O-Mania's seeing starfish
after that last one.
Let's finish him off with our special move.
Yeah, why not?
Take my hand.
Here it comes, y'all...
...the Purple Millionaire Ki-i-i-i-i-i-i-ck!
And Shark-O-Mania's out cold.
Somebody put that fish on ice before it stinks up the joint.
Folks, Tiger Millionaire and Purple Puma have done it again.
They are still your tag-team champions.
Will their special brand of jungle terror
ever come to an end?
Yeah! Don't ever stop!
Tiger Millionaire and Purple Puma forever!
Such dedication to teamwork and friendship. What?!
Hey.
It's been fun, but...I'm over this.
W-What's going on?
I'm through with this place.
Here's your belt back.
Hey, now. That mic is expensive.
You can't just -- Oh, no.
You're just gonna do that and leave?
Uh, sorry, everyone.
I guess this is over.
Bye, Mr. Smiley.
What an unbelievable shame, folks.
What?! That's it?
You can't quit now.
Mr. Smiley: What a sad and anticlimactic end
to one of the greatest tag-team careers
to ever grace the squared circle.
Got my Saturday nights back.
Did you really mean what you said
about being through with wrestling?
Come on, Steven.
Wasn't that match kind of boring?
We don't need wrestling to have fun anymore, right?
Uh, right.
Yeah.
Let's go home and get some grub.
Hey, Sadie. Hey, Lars.
Can I get the special?
Uh...
Tiger. Aah!
He left wrestling at the height of his career.
Why-y-y-y?
Huh. Why don't you just ask Steven?
You and your theory.
Steven is not Tiger.
Tiger's ripped and like seven feet tall.
Well, I heard Purple Puma didn't want to do it anymore.
So what?!
Just because Purple Puma quit doesn't mean Tiger had to.
I also heard Tiger didn't think of that.
Well, he should have.
It's the least he could do for his fans.
Hmm...
Oh, it is him, right?
Mr. Smiley: Now, I know these days, we're in a depression,
but underground wrestling is too big to fail.
We've got two new fighters on loan,
and they're here to collect.
Ladies and gentlemen, the Wolves of Wall Street.
We'll huff, we'll puff, and we'll blow your stocks down.
What a rip-off.
What's this?
It looks like we have a new challenger
making his way into the ring.
What mystery could possibly lie
beneath that identity-concealing shawl?
I don't believe it.
Tiger Millionaire, ladies and gentlemen!
You're wrong, Mr. Smiley.
Tiger Millionaire is gone forever.
He retired to his huge pile of money.
But he realized it didn't make him happy,
so here I am, ready to give back to the fans.
Tiger Philanthropist!
So, the millionaire becomes a philanthropist --
a person who gives money away.
But I ask you, can the Purple Puma's back-up make it solo?
Bring it on!
Hey, tough boy.
You need a loan to start a small business?
Oh, I'm actually pretty financially stable.
'Cause you've just been approved.
But I just said --
Mr. Smiley: Oh, my dang.
Billy Bank Assets just got a taste
of the Philanthropist business-loan elbow.
Howl Jones is still in this match, though.
He's gonna make a withdrawal.
Oh! Overdraft.
This should cover your medical bills.
What a generous wrestler.
Oh, what?
Looks like Shark-O-Mania is back for revenge
with a new partner -- the Sea Wasp,
which is a very poisonous type of jellyfish.
Ha. Looks like we'll have to give 'em the ol' Purple Pu--
Man, how's Tiger gonna get out of this fishy situation?
Oh. He hit them with a charitable take-donation.
And now a venture catapult-ist.
Did you see that?
He's paying for their medical bills, too.
It looks like this philanthropist is the real deal,
ladies and gentlemen.
No one is leaving here tonight unimpressed.
Hi, Lars.
Uh...What?
So...
How was your evening?
Fine, I guess.
Kind of boring.
What do you mean kind of boring?!
Why are you so worked up over how my night was?
Oh, uh...
well, I was wondering if you'd seen
any good wrestling matches lately.
Ha! Now that you mention it, no.
But I heard Tiger Millionaire was back.
He's your favorite, right?
Yeah, but he came back
as some lame Tiger Philharmonic donations thing,
which, honestly, is such a weird angle, you know?
The whole thing just felt so off.
What do you mean off?
He took off his tie, and he's throwing money at everybody?
It's like the sequel no one asked for.
What? It's the sequel you asked for.
Well, he just didn't seem into it, you know?
He used to care about his money.
Now he's just giving it away.
And he still just wins, like, every match.
Oh, I get it.
You want him to lose and keep his money, right?
No, I don't want him to lose, just --
What do you want him to do?!
Just tell me-e-e-e-e!
I don't know!
I don't even know what I want for breakfast half the time.
I'm a complex individual teenage boy.
Now get out of here and stop taking such a personal interest
in my happiness and well-being!
I don't get it.
I don't even know why I'm wrestling anymore.
I guess I'm doing it for Lars,
and he doesn't even care.
I liked it better when I was doing it for you.
But who needs it, you know?
I mean, I needed it when I felt like...I wasn't good enough.
But I-I don't feel like that anymore.
Do you?
No. No, that -- that's never why I was doing it.
I just liked that it was our thing we did together.
But you're right. It doesn't make sense anymore.
I think I should just do what you did --
just tell everybody I'm quitting
and leave like it's no big deal.
Ladies and gents, tonight is a very special night
here at the Beach City Wrestling Arena Dome and Building.
I'll let my good friend Tiger Mill--
I mean, Philanthropist explain.
Thank you, Mr. Smiley.
What now?
Tonight will mark my greatest
and finalest act of philanthropy.
Tonight, I am giving away the tag-team titles.
Whoever can grab them first can have them.
Boo! Philanthropy is lame!
Boo all you like. I don't care anymore.
These belts don't mean anything to me.
They never did.
I know that sound.
It's the Brothers Construction --
Concrete Heat and Chunk Truck.
So sad to see Tiger giving up those belts
without at least putting up a fight.
Whoa! It's the Good-Looking Guys' music.
They're back to finally claim the tag titles.
Looks like things are heating up in the ring.
Who will be the next tag-team champion?!
Whoa, there, Tiger.
Amethyst?
He's back!
The legend has returned to the ring!
Pu-u-u-rple Pu-u-u-ma!
Those belts aren't yours to give away.
Those times we wrestled together meant everything to me.
You can give away all the jungle bucks you want,
but I will not stand by and let you give up our memories.
Aww, what a display, ladies and gentlemen.
You came back.
I'm sorry.
This was our thing we did together,
and I just quit on you.
It's okay. You were right. We don't need this anymore.
Well, then how do you want to go out?
With a bang.
It looks like this fight for the belt is still on.
The Brothers Construction look like they're ready
to lay down a foundation of pain.
But, oh.
Shark-O-Mania is back again.
He's not even in the match.
Tiger Philanthropist is down. What?!
This isn't fair. Stop the match.
They're gonna be destroyed.
Both: Finish it.
Mr. Smiley: No!
The Good-Looking Gang hit the star-crossed lovers
on Puma and Tiger.
This is their chance.
The belts are hanging free and clear.
They've got it. It's official.
The Good-Looking Gang are
the new Beach City Underground Tag-Team Wrestling Champions.
This is truly the end for Tiger Millionaire and Purple Puma.
What a way to go out.
How can this be happening?!
It was just getting good!
You can't quit now!
Tiger!